clipzine.me 2014-11-21

# CLIPZINE: Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy describes CLIPZINE's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. CLIPZINE receives your information through our various web sites, SMS, APIs, applications, services and third-parties ("Services"). For example, you send us information when you use CLIPZINE from our web site, post or receive Message Data via SMS, add a CLIPZINE widget to your website, or access CLIPZINE from an application such as CLIPZINE for Mac, CLIPZINE for Android or Others. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by CLIPZINE in the South Korea or any other country where CLIPZINE operates. 

By using the Service, you hereby acknowledge and consent to the terms expressed hereunder. If you do not agree to any provision of the following Privacy Policy, then please do not use CLIPZINE. 

### Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration** : When you create or reconfigure a CLIPZINE account, you provide some personal information, legal guardian information (if you are not at least 14 year old), such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration. 

**Additional Information** : You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, your location, or a picture. You may customize your account with information such as a cell phone number for the delivery of SMS messages or your address book so that we can help you find CLIPZINE users you know. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional. 

**Location Information** : You may choose to note your location in your CLIPZINE profile. If you turn on your location, we may also save exact coordinates to help improve our service. You can control your location information settings in your account settings. 

**Log Data** : Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with our website, applications and advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. If we haven’t already deleted the Log Data earlier, we will either delete it or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months. 

**Links** : CLIPZINE may keep track of how you interact with links in Tweets across our Services including third party services and clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on. 

**Cookies** : Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. CLIPZINE may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

**Third Party Services** : CLIPZINE uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request. 

**Other Public Information** : Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public but we generally give you settings to make the information more private if you want. Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by CLIPZINE. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Consent** : We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your CLIPZINE account. 

**Service Providers** : We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy. 

**Law and Harm** : We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect CLIPZINE's rights or property. 

**Business Transfers** : In the event that CLIPZINE is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. 

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information** : We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public Data or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did). 

### Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. 

You can always review, correct, update, or change your Personal Information, by changing the relevant setting in your profile or account (if available). You can also permanently delete your CLIPZINE account. When your account is deactivated, it is not viewable on clipzine.me. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 14. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you are at least 14 years old. Should we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 14, we will delete such information from our records. In addition, we recommend that minors 14 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves over the Internet. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy, in which case we shall inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our website, www.clipzine.me/privacy.html. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Service constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

### Contact US

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@clipzine.me](mailto:contact@clipzine.me)

_Effective: January 14, 2013_
